Local 1199 Additional Records 5945
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Additional Records
1969-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 National Union of Hospital and Health Care Workers (NUCCSW)
5945
8.78 cubic feet
8.7 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5736599
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 18, 2000
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5510: Local 1199 Records 5651: Local 1199 Additional Records 5871: Local 1199 Additional Records 6347: 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Records
Health facilities -- Employees -- Labor unions; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees.; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. Local 1199 Drug & Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.)
5736599
- AIDS (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Applications for Membership, Dues Check-off List (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Attendance (Delegate, Meetings, Strikes) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Awards and Diplomas (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Ballots and Election Information (District and National) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Ballots, Withdrawal Cards, Applications, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Benefit Fund (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bread and Roses (National and District Cultural Affairs) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bread and Roses (National and District Cultural Affairs) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bread and Roses (National and District Cultural Affairs) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bread and Roses (National and District Cultural Affairs) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bread and Roses (National and District Cultural Affairs) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Brochures, Organizing, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Business Reply Cards and Authorizations (District 1199 NY) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Business Reply Cards and Authorizations (National) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Buttons, Stick-ons, Mail labels (District and National) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cartoons (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Certificate of Appreciation (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Certificates of Awards (Blank, undated) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Chapter Newsletters (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Check Voucher Request, ND (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Christmas Party (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Community Power Action, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Conferences (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, 1971-1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Contracts, Proposals (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Conventions (District and National) (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Credit Union (District) and Joseph Tauber Credit Union (District) and Joseph Tauber (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Cultural Affairs, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dances, Parties, Rallies, Boat rides, Raffles and Invitations (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Delegates Newsletters (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Delegates Newsletters and Correspondence (National and District) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Delegates Newsletters (Box 2, Folder 5)
- DRG Information, Medicare, ND (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Divisional Newsletters (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Drug Division Organizing (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Drug Division-Pathmark Campaign October-November, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Educational Materials, 1980-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 1199 Elections, Local ND (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 1199J (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 1199C Philadelphia (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 1199E (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 1199P (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 1199 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 1199 Election Fraud (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 1199 Elections (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Employment Office (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Employment Service (District) (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Employment Service, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Forms (blank) (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Forms and Cards, Prior to Spring, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Union Forms, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Forms and Form Letters (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Health and Safety-Manuals, Workers Guides (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Home Care (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Jesse Jackson (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Keswick Home for Incurables of Baltimore City/1199E, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Labels-National (Box 2, Folder 30)
- League of Registered Nurses (Promotional) (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Letterhead (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Letterhead and Envelopes (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Logos (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Membership Cards-Identification, ND (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Membership Services (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Mergers, SEIU (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous-Christmas Greetings (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Missing Children, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- National Rainbow Coalition ND (Box 3, Folder 7)
- National Organizing Campaigns (Box 3, Folder 8)
- National Union Promotional (Box 3, Folder 9)
- National Union-Merger, District 1199 struggle (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 1199 New York (Promotional) (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Newspaper Articles, 1970-1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Newsletters and Bulletins A-L (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Newsletters and Bulletins M-O (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Newsletters and Bulletins P-Z (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Nicaragua-Cuba (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Nominating Petitions for Delegate (Box 3, Folder 17)
- NYCOSH Al Vahn, Zoilo, Reale (Box 3, Folder 18)
- OSHA, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Ohio Health Care Professionals Campaign (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Ohio Campaign, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Organizing-Very Early (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Organizing (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Organizing (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Organizing Leaflets [folder 1 of 2], 1974-1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Organizing Leaflets [folder 2 of 2], 1974-1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Organizing Work Assignment Sheets, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Parties, Union Affairs, 1985-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Political-AGI/Prop (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Political Materials, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Politics (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Press Clips 1969-early 70s, 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Press Releases (Home Care, etc.) (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Publicity, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Publicity, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Publicity-Organizing Leaflets, 1970-1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Publicity-Organizing Leaflets-Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Publicity-Organizing Leaflets-Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Publicity-Rallies, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Puerto Rico (National) (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Political Action, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Recreational Activities, 1971-1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Reprints (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Retirees PAC, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Retired Members (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Retired Members Before 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Rivera, Dennis, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- RNs Organizing News (Box 5, Folder 6)
- RN Division (Box 5, Folder 7)
- RN Elections, Organizing (Box 5, Folder 8)
- RNs Newsletters (Box 5, Folder 9)
- RN Newsletters and Bulletins (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Safety and Health (District and National) (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Senior Citizens and Retirees (National and District) Death Memorials (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Senior Citizen News (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Songs (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Stickers 1992, ND (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Strike Information and Firings (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Sample Ballot (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Senior Citizen News (Box 5, Folder 18)
- SNUB (Box 5, Folder 19)
- South Africa Political Action (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Subcontracted Jobs (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Tickets, Invitations (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Tickets and Flyers for 1199 Functions (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Tickets and Raffles, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Training and Upgrading, Education Seminars (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Training Fund (Box 5, Folder 26)
- University of New Mexico Hospital, Benalillo County Medical Center/1199NM 1985 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Oversized materials including posters, broadsides, and flyers (Box 6)
- Oversized materials including posters, broadsides, and flyers (Box 7)
- Fight Health Care Cuts (Box 8)
- Fight Health Care Cuts (Box 9)